get in the car
Kansana I'll give you a ride, I said I won't go
Kansana
I got there by metro, obviously
There are things in life that are better not to see, please
no
there is something that should not be seen
I've seen these lines since I was born
tell me how it really was no what are you
nothing personal, she is dear to me but we have a business relationship
over time I began to understand
what do the lines mean
what are you writing
and I also knew that no one except me could see them
damned doomed to see what is hidden from others
the daughter who made her mother go crazy and killed her father
the red lines didn't seem like anything special
but gradually they made sense
when I realized that the ability
seeing lines can lead to someone's death
I decided to close
mouth and eyes
I wanted to end this
but couldn't die
I always survived, it was like I was being bullied
and I was left completely alone
then I decided
since I'm destined to live
I have to find out where these lines come from
who created them
Does anyone else see them besides me?
and
how to get rid of this curse
hey is anyone home
I moved into the building opposite a couple of days ago
I wanted to treat my neighbors
pies, but few people eat them these days
that's why I brought fruit, you like it
I hardly ate fruit when I was a child.
and when I grew up
I realized that we simply couldn’t afford them
I'll leave it near the door, eat it or it'll spoil
hey sorry about that
I'll tell you later
you scratched my car again
what's wrong with you
why did you come so early
I don't know myself
decided to try myself as an uncle
it wasn't even worth trying, you're talking about your niece
schoolchildren have become uncontrollable and even arrogant, what can we do?
she only has me what will happen to her when you get married
gets married
my wedding
you'll come
why do I need this
Well, we're colleagues
what
I completely forgot what I had to do
I thought you didn’t care who you sleep with, but you’re picky
I'm sorry
Sana, come on, be a good girl
and why did you run so far
hey look me in the eyes
here you get it
you were warned, don't be arrogant, look
how are you Sana it hurts you, lift it up, come on
Sona
instead of bringing money I went to complain
it's you
pick her up
what are you Sana
we're not done yet
get up let's get up
that means your uncle is a policeman
then everything is clear
that's why you don't answer calls
damn you're heavy
score
funny
you'll knock again
and I'll throw you out of here
got it
arrived
who is she woman 29 years old lived 1
worked as a manager in a cafe next door
no brothers or sisters, only parents live outside the city
guy is still unknown, need to check
the house is such a mess and her things are neat
and the body is clean
it feels like everything is set up
there is a delicious popular cafe there
only locals know about it
check
yes
Detective Khan, we took a statement from a tenant on the 1st floor.
he said that he saw how to go to a woman’s apartment
a man in a helmet in a helmet was rising
says a man who looks like a courier
I just don't understand
what was his motive anyway?
money on the spot
no signs of violence
and the victim does not look like a conflicted person
maybe he's a psychopath and happened to pass by
what kind of delivery service is this?
the woman often ordered food but on the wrong day
and her attitude
found out something
they say she had a man
but they broke up about a year ago
find him
good evening, news anchor Anjion here
today afternoon July 25th
Another murder occurred in a residential complex in Sinodon
body of a young woman discovered
This is the 3rd incident in the last month
The police have still not been able to establish
identity of the perpetrator clues
no, the investigation has reached a dead end
local residents are extremely concerned about the increase in crime
more details in the paksongwon report
this afternoon in 1 of the apartments in the area
sinudon young woman found dead
death was due to strangulation; traces of forced entry were found
a case of spontaneous murder during a robbery has been opened
not long ago in the area
sinudon, a single woman in her 30s was killed
people with hundreds of lines are quite rare
but it’s impossible not to notice the owner of the 1st line
especially the one who shows
excessive interest in the crime scene
no I didn't hear anything strange
I've been here all the time lately
Couriers ride on motorcycles
I thought someone just ordered delivery
you called the emergency service
man in a helmet in front of my house
yes I listen to you say
hello
The topic of today's lesson is ecological balance in village 1
wolves began to often attack livestock
residents raised the alarm and asked for permission to hunt
what happened next
the wolves began to hide like this
in the end he won't come
what's there
what is it there
open some package
clothes
what is this
scared
didn't go to school
uncle
give me money
I'll take it tomorrow and shoot more
how much can you give
what's wrong with your face
you were beaten
what do you care
how much will you give why do you need money
juke what's the matter I got a call last night
reported a man wearing a helmet
Did we mention that we suspect the courier?
Where did they call from for a minute?
Sinudon residential complex Vanson building b
isn't this your address building b
detective prude police panju anyone home
oh never before near me
there was no man with so many lines
hello
don't even try, it won't open
everyone knows that she is a recluse, they even take out the trash after her
goodbye
I won't take much time it was you who called the police
if you saw something please tell me
your testimony can be very useful for the investigation
you are schoolgirls parents at home
it seemed to me
that I misunderstood and called the police
can you tell me more about what happened?
I saw a man in a helmet enter the building opposite
I thought the woman was in danger
woman
your neighbor
she moved to apartment 204
there's so much going on lately
it turned out
they are dating
so you're schoolgirls shouldn't you
what kind of youth are these days?
how does she know where I live
bitch
who is this? let's go, I won't pay for you
let's go somewhere else
oh cool thing
how much does it cost
I didn’t buy it father or mother stop leaving me alone
I'm interested
listen
The woman who was killed in Sinudon used to have a man
o john mim teacher at panju high school lives at
Vanson building b apartment 303
don't you think it's suspicious
and also a murder last month
that woman went to the 1st gym with John Min
they crossed paths
apartment 303 photos available
she won't open up, everyone knows she's a recluse
they even take out the trash after her
man from 303rd
knew both victims
that's a coincidence really yeah
this cannot be ignored
I'm listening
got it
I'll drop by somewhere, go ahead
where to
you are Khan Hasan's guardian
the new nurse left for just a minute and he disappeared
we are searching the entire hospital area
you are scared but please wait
or maybe
it would be better
come here rather, why did you get in there? it’s dangerous
get down you might fall
come down come on
what the hell is this
I'll be here soon weird
what are you talking about are you already there
what's strange what
hello dansik
oh dansik
1 left
damn
mom
are you here
John Min
how are you doing
why did you come
this is the only way we can be saved
that's enough
recluse
want to kill
try it
a
why are you shaking so much
come on hit me
chickened out
yes
now you
what nonsense about salvation
where are my glasses damn where are my glasses
are you alive
where are my glasses
get up quickly my glasses
I'm planning to run away, let me go
let me in
what is this
야
에이
it will be much better without you damn die
line line disappears
onlineline
that man he could see the lines too
but how
you don't need to go to the hospital
that dead man
why do you need glasses at night
do you know each other
don't come in without money
I look like an ATM
at school
something happened
tell me
what will this change?
you need to deal with the problem, what are you doing and how exactly
what are you going to do
pretend to be a guardian and go to this school yes
you'll disappear again
like you care
so that's what you think
passed
by the way
we studied together
her mother killed her father and ran away, didn’t know
thank you
thank you for the first time the thought occurred to me
that the ability to see lines can save lives
so
what should I do now
Be careful not to fall under the car
guys we have a new student in our class her name is shin hyun hyap
with these glasses you can see something
red lines you
you see them too
why bother with this?
we caught the killer, something doesn’t add up, so what?
I don’t understand why they had to kill the glasses
you'll keep them of course
no shame or conscience, if I were you I would be ashamed
what do you mean Sana
violence is not the answer, I will kill her
between the lines
everyone gets red for reasons
there's nowhere else to hide
I think we just gotta say
between the lines
what is real what is not
how are you so sure
still insecure by myself
how could we know